UPPI GOLD PARK
MESSY
LIVE MINATO'S ROOM
Spring
MEMORIES LINKED TO THE CLIMATE
SHOCKED
STICK
ZONED OUT
UPPI SHOW
YOU CAN TAKE PICTURES!
BIRTHDAY STICKER
HAHAHA
CLICK CLICK
UPPI PIN SET 680 YEN
(TAX EXCLUDED)
HOUSE OF HORRORS
HORROR
BANG
DRIP
ROUTE
EXIT
UGH...
JUST THE TWO OF YOU
THUMP THUMP THUMP
UPPI SAMBA!
*IN FACT, HE'S BEEN EXCITED SINCE YESTERDAY
PRIZE
THE REAL ONE
PUFFY
NOT USED TO BEING CELEBRATED
PUFFY FLUFFY
WARM
SQUEEZE
SWIFT
BAM
COME BACK AGAIN
STARE
PAT PAT
SILENCE
STUNNED...
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
(ADMIRATION FOR TALL PEOPLE)
GRADE 2 CLASS 2 NUMBER 2
MEW MEW MEW
GRADE 2 CLASS 2 NUMBER 22
MEW MEW MEW MEW
SQUEEZE
THRILLED
GRADE 2 CLASS 1
LOVES HAVING FUN
LOVES BEING ALONE
HIS FRIEND
"SOMEONE YOU KNOW"
SQUEEZE
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
STILL HERE
COMPLETE CHANGE
("YOU'RE THE ONE TO ASK" LOOK)
USUALLY TRYING TO BE CAREFUL...
NOW TALKING CASUALLY
MEITEN HIGH SCHOOL SPORTS FESTIVAL
CHEER SQUAD RECRUITMENT
GLANCE
BAM
SELF-PRACTICE TIME
BLUE SQUAD: CLASS 1 AND 2
RED SQUAD: CLASS 3 AND 4
INTUITIVE
EEK!
RELIEVED
POKE
JEEZ
THUMP!
HEH HEH
CONSIDERATE INTEREST
CHATTER, CHATTER
*NEARSIGHTED